OP
ED
Ashirogi
Hiramaru
Aoki
Eiji
Arai
The participants of the Leaders Fest are...
リーダーズフェスタに エントリーしてるのは
Arai, Eiji, Aoki, Hiramaru, and us.
新井先生 エイジ 蒼樹さん 平丸さん
それに俺たち
Five spots are already taken.
もう5枠決まってる
The deadline will change depending on what spot we're in,
何番目に載るかで違ってくるけど
but since we also have PCP to deal with, how far in advance should we prepare the manuscript?
「PCP」連載しながらだと 締め切り どのくらい前に原作必要
Shuujin.
シュージン
Will you let me handle this one-shot?
この読切 俺にやらせてくれないか
I want to see how far I can get by myself.
1人で どこまでできるか やってみたいんだ
By yourself?
1人で
Shuujin, you just said to Hattori that you're Ashirogi Mutou all the way.
シュージン さっき服部さんに 自分はあくまで亜城木夢叶
That you didn't want to cause me trouble by doing Rabuta.
「恋太」をやる事で 俺に迷惑かけたくないって言ってくれたろ
I was happy.
うれしかった
I don't want to drag you down, either.
俺も シュージンの足引っ張りたくない
I don't want PCP's quality to suffer
because of this one-shot. Or Rabuta's, either.
読切をやる事で 「PCP」はもちろん 「恋太」の質が落ちたら困る
I want to grow.
俺も もっと成長したい
I'll just do as much as I can.
やれるところまででいいんだ やってみたい
I want to try it!
With PCP still running, you'll work on Rabuta, and I'll handle the one-shot's storyboard.
「PCP」を連載しながら シュージンは「恋太」 俺は読切のネーム
If we can pull this off, we'll expand our horizons.
もし これができれば 幅が広がる
Ashirogi Mutou will become something greater!
亜城木夢叶が 確実に大きくなる
You're right.
だな
Ashirogi
Hiramaru
Even if we're working on different manga, we're still Ashirogi Mutou!
別の作品をやっていても 俺たちは「亜城木夢叶」
Yeah!
A special one-shot with center
color spread on page 45
Rabuta & Peace
Original work: Kido Takaaki
Artist: Shiratori Shun
ano ne moshimo ima sugu ni kimi no moto he to
Hey, if I could go to where you are right now
ikeru naraba kono koe ga nakunattemo ii ya
then I could accept losing my voice
mezasu basho ga amari ni mo tooku
The goals I've set myself seem impossible to reach,
boku wa mou michi ni mayoisou da
and I feel lost on my path
kowareta jishaku wo ate ni shiteru n da
I'm relying on a broken compass and hiding in another's shadow
dareka no kage ni kakurete sa
nanika wo te ni ireru tame nanika wo tebanasu nante koto wo
If we keep letting go of some things in order to find something else,
tsuzukete mo kitto bokura wa otona ni wa narenai
then I'm convinced we can never grow up
narenai
Never
Punch and Independence
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神字幕组---
台本:共由先生         翻译:   poopy    虫    繁化:烨语
校对：Astro      时间轴：福尔摩斯的手杖
Sun
Mon
Tues
Wed
Thur
Fri
What happened, Mashiro?!
どうしちゃったんですか
真城先生
Takagi?!
高木先生
You two were full of energy last week!
先週は2人ともすごいやる気 出してたのに 今日は一体
What happened?
Oh, sorry.
ごめん
I can't think of anything besides Rabuta and PCP.
僕は 「恋太」と「PCP」で頭いっぱいで
And Mashiro is trying to come up with another story.
真城は真城で 違う話 考えてるから
Huh? Mashiro is also working on two manga?
What should I do for the one-shot...?
読切 何を描けばいいか 全然 思い浮かばない
I can't think of anything!
That's great, but...
それは すごいですけど
Hey, I'm going out for a bit.
すみません ちょっと出てきます
Saikou...
サイコー
What can I draw? What am I good at?
僕に描けるもの
得意とするものは何だ
After my uncle died, all I did was sit at home playing video games.
おじさんが死んでからは 家で ゲームばかり
And after I decided to be a manga artist with Shuujin, all I've done aside from school is bury myself in manga.
シュージンとマンガ家 目指してからは
学校以外はほとんど屋内でマンガ漬け
I've never done anything out of the ordinary.
変わった事なんて何もしてない
Unlike Shuujin, sci-fi or mystery is impossible for me.
シュージンみたいにSFや推理ものなんて無理だ
And unlike Fukuda and Shiratori, I don't really have any hobbies.
福田さんや白鳥君みたいに 趣味があるわけでも
What do I have?
僕には 何が
What do I like?
僕が好きなものは
I like...
好きな
This can work!
いける
We're leaving!
お疲れさまでした
Have a good New Year's!
Something I like? It can only be one thing!
僕の好きなもの これしかない
Shiratori, make sure you visit your parents!
ちゃんと おうちに帰るのよ
Okay.
はい
Mashiro, you should at least say goodbye to them!
もう真城 「お疲れさま」くらい言いなさいよ
It's the last time you'll see them this year!
今年の最後だってのに
あっ ごめん お疲れさま
Sorry! Goodby—
They've already left!
もう帰っちゃったっつの
Are you still thinking about what to do for the one-shot?
まだ 読切 何描くのか悩んでんのか
If so, I can think of some ideas—
何なら 俺が原案考えても
I've got it already.
いや 決まった
Once an idea hits you, the rest comes quickly!
ひらめいちゃえば あとは早いね
Wh-What're you gonna do?
何 描くんだよ
A love story.
恋愛もの
That's not Ashirogi Mutou's style!
亜城木夢叶っぽくない
How'd you end up picking a love story?!
恋愛ものって 何で そうなるんだよ
Because the thing I like most is Azuki.
俺が一番好きなのは亜豆だから
That's it?
だから
At first, they simply gaze at the person they like.
最初は好きな人を見てるだけなんだ
Like me and Azuki.
俺と亜豆みたいに 始まり方は
It starts with him wondering, "Does that girl like me?"...
He's off in his own world now.
なんか入り込んじゃってるけど
But it may actually work.
いや でも アリかも
What?!
It's rare to find a romantic who
loves as earnestly as Saikou does.
サイコーくらいロマンチストで 一途な恋愛してるやつ 珍しいわけだし
I see.
そっか
Maybe a love story'll work.
恋愛もの いいかもね
I want to compete with this!
俺 これで勝負してみたい
How's that?
どう
Thanks!
ありがとうございます
It's good!
面白いです
I'll make this into a storyboard.
これで ネームにします
Finally, we've got the first chapter of Rabuta in the bag.
やっと「恋太」1話UP
We only need two more chapters to
submit it to the serialization committee.
連載会議に出すにはあと2話か
When is the committee?
連載会議って いつなのよ
Mid-February.
2月の中旬
But since we've also got PCP to worry about, I have to get it done before New Year's.
どっちにしろ 「PCP」があるから 正月中に上げないと駄目
You're on break until January 11th, right?
休みは 11日までよね
Yeah, and the New Year's party is on the 12th.
そう 12日 新年会だし
Takagi, we could shoot for the April committee instead of the February one, if you'd like.
高木先生 2月じゃなく4月の会議でも いいですから
No, I'll do it.
いや やる
I did put on that big show in front of your mom, after all.
白鳥君のお母さんの前で あんな大見得 切ったんだし
So if you don't go to the New Year's party, you could pull it off, right?
じゃあ 新年会行かないでやれば いいんじゃない
Well, we kinda have to go to that...
いや あれは行っとかないと
I can't do it!
できね
Um, I'll go home and make a clean copy of chapter one!
僕 帰って1話目 清書します
Yeah, go for it...
頑張って
So, what's the deal?
で 何に悩んでんだ
I can picture the guy's point of view by comparing it with my own,
男子サイドは 自分と照らし合わせてイメージできるんだけど
but the girl's...
女子サイドがな
Ask me anything!
何でも聞いてよ
Like what?
何を
Like about a-girl's-heart!
女の子のキ モ チ
I'll think of it on my own.
自分で考えます
Meanie! Then how about asking Miho?
ひどい
じゃあ 美保に聞けば
You're probably styling the heroine after her anyways, right?
どうせ美保みたいな自分好みのヒロインなんでしょ
Asking Azuki something like that would be too embarrassing!
亜豆に そういう事聞くの恥ずかしいだろ
I'll be here every day until the storyboard's
completed, so feel free to ask me for advice.
ネームが出来るまでは 毎日来るから いつでも相談しろよな
R-Right. Thanks.
悪いな
I can't do the storyboard.
ネーム出来ない
The storyboard for chapter two of Rabuta isn't done, either.
俺もまだ「恋太」の2話のネーム出来てねよ
Are we really going to the New Year's party in this kind of mood?
こんな気分で新年会か
It might actually cheer us up.
気分転換になっていいかもな
Yuujirou!
雄二郎 てめっ
You said there was no point in entering the Leader's Fest, you bastard!
人気作家読切祭に エントリーする意味ねえって言ったよな
GIRI is popular! There's no need for you to enter!
「GIRI」がうけてんだ 必要ない
So why did Ashirogi and Master Niizuma, whose
manga are more popular than GIRI, enter anyways?
じゃあ 何で 「GIRI」よりうけてる新妻師匠と亜城木君がエントリーしてるんだ
Isn't that strange?!
おかしいだろ
Fukuda...
福田さん
I'll do it, too!
俺も描く
Good evening.
こんばんは
Look, it's both of the "Jack Girls."
ミスジャックが2人おそろいで
Hey Fukuda, that's rude!
こら 福田君 そういう言い方 失礼だぞ
GOOD AFTERNOON!
グッドアフタヌーン
It looks like all of you are entering the Leader's Fest.
みんな リーダーズフェスタにエントリーしてるらしいが
I'm in, too! Game on!
俺もだ
勝負だ
Wait, Fukuda...!
いや 福田君
It's noisy over here.
騒がしいな
What's wrong, Yuujirou?
どうした 雄二郎
Chief Editor!
編集長 どうせやるなら 順位をつけて下さい
Why don't you rank us while you're at it?
What are you talking about?
何の話だ
Chief, Fukuda was talking about entering the Leader's Fest...
編集長 福田君も リーダーズフェスタにエントリーしたいと
Hey, don't get in my way!
こら 邪魔すんな
You're getting ahead of yourself!
突っ走りすぎなんだよ 君は
You could at least rank us privately!
どうせ 裏では順位つけてんだろ
Come on, now!
あのな
Very well.
いいだろう 福田君の案に乗ろうじゃないか
Let's do as Fukuda suggests.
After all the one-shots have run, we'll put out a survey so the readers can vote on which one they liked best.
全読切発表後 読者アンケートを取り
誰の作品が一番面白かったか 決める
I understand. Aoki and I are planning on a love story.
分かりました
私と蒼樹さんは恋愛マンガにするつもりです
What?! A love story manga? You and Aoki?
恋愛マンガ
蒼樹さんと 岩瀬も
Is something wrong with that?
私が恋愛マンガ おかしいですか
No, that's not it. It's just that we were also—
いや そうじゃなくて 僕たちも
Sounds interesting!
面白いです 今回 僕も愛が勝つマンガです
This time, I will also enter with a
manga about love conquering all!
勝負です
No way!
うそ
You, too?
新妻さんも
Yes!
はい
During the audition for NATURAL,
「NATURAL」のオーディションの時
Mashiro was really cool when he came to take away his girlfriend!
真城先生が 彼女を さらっていったの超かっこよかったです
I'll write something like that!
ああいうのを やりたいです
These are supposed to be shounen manga, but these guys...
少年マンガだってのにどいつもこいつも
Fine, dammit!
分かったよ
くそっ 俺も恋愛ものでいく
I'll do a love story, too!
What?
All the authors participating in the
Leader's Fest will compete with love stories.
リーダーズフェスタに参加するマンガ家が 全員 恋愛もので競う
It's an interesting experiment.
面白い試みですね
Did someone call me?
今 誰か僕を呼んだか
Hiramaru, this is bad!
平丸 まずい
Aoki is here!
蒼樹さんがいるぞ 目を覚ませ
Get it together!
What do you think, Hiramaru?
平丸先生は どう思いますか
Wh-What a coincidence!
き 奇遇だな 僕も
I was just thinking about doing a shounen manga version of Kimi ni Todoke....
「君に届け」の少年マンガバージョンをちょうど やろうと思ってたところなので
Sounds good.
いいじゃないですか
Arai!
新井先生
Actually, back when I was a contributor, I did love comedies all the time.
実は 私 投稿時代ラブコメばかり描いていたんですよ
Interesting.
面白い
It's not the Super Leader's Fest...
人気作家読切祭ではなく
It's the Super Leader's Love Fest.
人気作家恋愛読切祭だな
A competition to see who can create the best love story?
全員 恋愛もので誰が1位を取るか勝負
I'm stepping outside to make a call!
ちょっと外で電話してくる
What? The party's about to start!
もう新年会 始まるぞ
Connected
Azuki Miho
Mashiro? Is something wrong?
真城君 どうかした
Connected
Azuki Miho
Azuki! You've been aware of me since 4th grade, right?
Connected
Azuki Miho
亜豆さん
亜豆さんは 小4の時から僕の事を意識してたんですよね
Huh?
Yeah.
Connected
Azuki Miho
Does "aware" mean "in love"?
意識してたって 好きって事
Mashiro, why are you asking about this?
真城君 何で急にそんな事
Connected
Azuki Miho
Oh, sorry.
Connected
Azuki Miho
ごめん
I'm doing a one-shot.
今度 読切 描く事になって
Seven authors will publish love stories, and they'll all be ranked.
7人の作家が 恋愛もので作品を発表して順位を決めるんだ
I think it was love at first sight.
一目ぼれだったと思う
Connected
Azuki Miho
I liked you after taking just one look at you.
一目見て真城君を好きになった
Azuki Miho
Connected
Ask me anything. I'll answer honestly.
何でも聞いて ちゃんと答える
L-Love at first sight... what was it about me that you fell for?
ひ 一目ぼれって 僕のどこに
Love at first sight doesn't follow any rhyme or reason.
一目ぼれだもん 理屈とかじゃない
The atmosphere that emanated from you... it fit me perfectly.
真城君から出てる雰囲気 空気
それが自分に ピッタリ合ってる
That's what I thought.
そう思った
I see.
そっか これを生かして
I'll use this!
Thanks, Azuki.
亜豆さん ありがとう
I'll make this one-shot great!
今度の読切 絶対 面白くする
Kengo is watching me,
like I thought.
Kengo is watching me, just like I thought!
She realized that
I'm watching her!
She realized that I'm watching her!
She realized that
I'm watching her!
Kengo is watching me,
like I thought.
I know she'll
look at me again.
She'll look at me again...
If I turn
around and
our eyes meet...
If I turn around and our eyes meet...
I have
to be
brave
and not
look
away.
I have to be brave and not look away!
Have to
be brave...
Have to be brave...
Turn
This is the
moment
our first
crush
became
love.
I know it!
This is the moment our first crush turned into love.
It really is a love story!
本当に恋愛ものだ
It's pretty good!
結構 面白いよ
Really?!
本当ですか
You did it!
やったな
What is it?
どうした
Actually, Mashiro came up with this one.
実は この話は 真城主導で
I see.
なるほど
That's why it has a different style than normal.
それで いつもと作風が違うのか
Personally, I think it's good,
個人的には 面白いと思ったが
but I can't predict how Jack readers will respond to this kind of outlook on love.
この恋愛観に 「ジャック」の読者がどう反応するか 判断つきかねるな
It's worth a shot, though.
でも やってみる価値はある
I think there are some parts that need polishing, but let's go with this.
もう少し練り直した方がいい所もあるが これで進めよう
Okay!
はい
Now, Takagi, show me chapter two of Rabuta.
じゃあ 高木君「恋太」の2話を見せてくれ
This is no good.
駄目だな
Peace isn't acting like a dog anymore.
これでは ピースが犬らしくない
Takagi, I know you're good at advancing the story by having the characters think deeply about things,
高木君はキャラに ものを深く考えさせて 話を進めていくのがうまいが
but this time, that's working against you.
今回ばかりは それが裏目に出ている
Peace is a dog.
ピースは犬だぞ
I'm not saying he needs to think completely like a dog, but you at least need to simplify his feelings.
もっと犬の気持ちになれとは言わないが ピースの思考は 単純な方がいい
I understand.
分かりました
I'll start again from scratch.
全体的に考え直してみます
Good luck.
頑張ってくれ
And now, I have a message for you.
それじゃあ 連絡事項
On February 16th, in Issue #11,
2月16日発売の11号で 「PCP」連載50回1周年記念の巻頭カラーだ
the 50th chapter of PCP will be getting a front-page
color spread to commemorate its one-year anniversary.
I see. A year, huh?
そうか1年か
We knew that, of course. But it's still great to hear!
分かってた事だけど うれしいな
Yeah!
Your contract price and the per-manuscript
payments will also be raised come February.
契約金と2月からの原稿料UPも決まった
All right!
やったな
イッテ
Let's see. Payment is per page, so 19
pages, four times a month, would equal...
えっと 原稿料は1ページごとだから
19ページで×19 月4回として
Don't calculate that here!
そんな計算 今 すんなよ
No, you're pros. You should be happy.
いや プロなんだ 大いに喜べ
Also, the second drama CD has been confirmed.
それとドラマCDの第2弾も決まった
This Azuki Miho that you recommended is now pretty popular.
2人が推薦してくれた亜豆美保さんの評判もいい
She's gotten a lot of work since then.
あれから仕事も増えてるそうだ
Your first anniversary will also be celebrated at the serialization awards ceremony.
めでたく1周年を迎えたって事で 連載表彰式もある
We really made it to a year.
本当に1年やったんだな
Yeah!
Everything's going well.
何もかも うまくいっている
But...
でも
Niizuma
Eiji  Ltd.
I'm amazed at how you can write three works simultaneously.
しかし よく同時進行で3作品描けるな
Doing a bunch of stuff at once is fun!
いろんなの描けて楽しいですけど
A bunch of stuff?
いろいろって
Why is it okay for you to do that, but not okay for Takagi to write the story for Rabuta & Peace?
自分はよくて 何で高木君が「恋太」の原作やるのは駄目なんだ
Huh?
はい
I'm talking about what you said before!
この前そう言ってたじゃないか
Rabuta isn't by Ashirogi.
「恋太」は亜城木先生の作品じゃないです
It's true that Takagi only wrote the story.
確かに高木君は 原作だけだけど
That's not what I mean.
そういう意味じゃないですけど
Huh?
Rabuta & Peace is by Shiratori Shun.
「恋太＆ピース」は白鳥シュン先生の作品です
I have no time!
ああ 時間ね
You don't necessarily have to make
the February serialization committee, right?
2月の連載会議じゃなくてもいいんでしょ
Shuujin, let's both do our best!
シュージン お互い 頑張ろうぜ
Easy for you to say. I'm the one who practically has to start from scratch.
お互いって言うけど 俺の方はある意味 全部直しだからな
Don't act like this doesn't involve you.
「俺の方」って言うなよ
We're going to release this as an Ashirogi Mutou manga.
これも亜城木夢叶の作品として発表するんだから
You may say that, but you did all the work on that one.
そうは言っても
そっちはほとんどサイコーが作ってるんだし
What I'm working on is Shiratori Shun's story.
俺が作ってるのは白鳥シュンの原作だぜ
Can you say that this is Ashirogi Mutou?
これで 亜城木夢叶って言えるのか
What's wrong?
どうしたんだよ
Are we going to be okay?
俺たち 本当に これでいいのか
Normally, wouldn't we both be
desperately working on that one-shot?
本来なら その読切を2人で必死にやるべきじゃないのかって
Shuujin...
シュージン
PCP won't become an anime.
「PCP」は アニメにならない
Even so, if I work hard on this and Rabuta
becomes an anime, would that make you happy?
だからといって 「恋太」頑張って こっちが アニメになったりしたら
素直に喜べるか
That's...
それは
I guess I was selfish for wanting to start another manga besides PCP so we could get an anime adaptation.
「PCP」以外にもう1本描いて アニメ化なんて俺のわがままだよな
That's not what I'm saying!
そうは言ってないだろ
If you really want an anime adaptation, what we're doing now is strange!
本当に アニメ化したいなら こんな状況 おかしい
I'm telling you to be more selfish!
もっと わがままを通せって言ってんだ
Don't fight!
ケンカは やめなさい
Akito, apologize to Mashiro!
秋人さん 真城に謝りなさい
Just because you're frustrated with your work doesn't mean you can take it out on Mashiro!
自分のがうまくいかないからって
何 真城に当たってんのよ
That's not it...
いや そうじゃないって
Shiratori, I can't write Rabuta unless I observe dogs up close.
白鳥君 犬の事もっと観察しないと 「恋太」書けない
Can I come over?
ちょっと そっちに行ってもいいかな
Well, I'm leaving.
じゃあ 行ってくる
Wh-What was that about?
な 何なの
What should I do? Should I go stop him?
どうしよう 止めてこようか
I can still—
まだ 間に合う
It's fine.
いいよ
It makes sense to be with Peace when he's writing Rabuta.
「恋太」を書くには ピースと一緒にいた方がいいのは確かだ
Are you really okay with that?
本当にいいの
Do you really think it's a good thing for him to write Rabuta?
真城は本心で 秋人さんが「恋太」書いた方がいいと思ってるの
It's not right for me to stop Shuujin from broadening his abilities as an author.
シュージンの原作者としての幅が広がるのを 俺が止めるのは おかしいよ
If he does, it'll improve Ashirogi Mutou as well.
幅が広がれば それが亜城木夢叶に返ってくる
But what will you do if it doesn't?
返ってこなかったら どうすんのよ
What if Rabuta does well, and he works on that full time?
「恋太」の方が うまくいっちゃって そっちばっかりになったら
Even if that happens, Shuujin wouldn't do anything to hurt Ashirogi Mutou.
そうなったとしてもシュージンは 亜城木夢叶をないがしろにはしない
I'll believe in him.
俺は シュージンを信じる
Taking care of a dog must be pretty hard.
犬飼うのって大変なんだな
You have to play with him and take him for walks every day.
毎日 散歩させて 遊んでやって
The toughest part is paying for his food.
一番大変なのは 餌代ですよ
Peace is worried.
ピースが心配してる
Dogs can tell what you're feeling from your expression.
犬は表情から人の心情を読み取りますからね
They know when you tell a lie, too.
うそも 見抜きますし
Really?
I guess the manga you made isn't so far from reality.
マンガで描いてある事 あながち うそじゃないんだな
That's right.
そうですよ
Otherwise, I wouldn't have been able to come up with Rabuta & Peace.
じゃなきゃ 「恋太＆ピース」思いつきませんでした
I see.
そっか
Good night!
お疲れさまでした
You, too!
お疲れさま
Akito didn't come to the studio today, either.
秋人さん 今日も仕事場来なかったわね
Yeah.
He's been gone all week!
今週 ずっとじゃん
And today's the meeting and the
deadline for turning in your manuscript.
それに 今日 原稿渡して そのまま打ち合わせよね
Yeah.
Oh, is it time for your regular love letter from Miho?
あら 美保との愛の定期通信 来ちゃった
It's from Shuujin.
シュージンからだ
Takagi Akito
No Subject
I'll discuss PCP outside with Hattori.
You concentrate on the one-shot.
Wh-What's with this?
何これ 来ない気
He doesn't feel like coming?
And he's just sending a text instead of calling in person!
しかも電話じゃなくてメールで一方的に
He's being thorough about this.
徹底してるな
I'm calling him!
秋人さんに電話する
No!
やめろ
Don't.
やめてくれ
But...
でも
You'd better not involve yourself in this.
香耶ちゃんは口出さない方がいい
Takagi told me he would meet me to discuss PCP one-on-one,
高木君は 「PCP」の打ち合わせは僕と2人で
and to meet you later at your studio to discuss the one-shot.
そのあと読切の打ち合わせは真城君と仕事場で やってくれって言ってきたんだが
I see.
そうですか
Mashiro, it's 11 PM...
真城さん もう11時ですけど
Oh, you can go.
あっ 上がって下さい
We're leaving, then!
じゃあ 失礼します
Good night.
失礼します
Good work today.
お疲れさま
Mashiro.
真城先生 ちょっとお話が
I have something to talk to you about.
What?
何
I'd like to quit this assistant job at the end of the week.
今週いっぱいで アシスタント辞めさせてほしいんですけど
Why?
何で
If Takagi is really aiming for a serialization, I think I should stop being an assistant.
高木先生が 本気で連載狙うなら アシスタントは 辞めるべきだと
Okay.
分かった 確かにそうだよな
That's true.
I'll start looking for a replacement.
代わりのアシは何とか見つけるよ
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
And Kaya, is it really okay with you?
それと 香耶さん ほんとに いいんですか
That Takagi wants to stay over at my place for a while to observe Peace, I mean.
高木先生 しばらくうちに泊まってピースを観察したいって
What?!
He didn't tell me that!
聞いてない
What? Really?
そうなんですか
Mashiro, what should I do?
真城先生 どうすれば
You should let Takagi do what he wants.
高木の好きなようにさせればいい
Just think about making Rabuta better,
白鳥君も 「恋太」を面白くする事だけを考えて
and don't worry about me.
僕に気を遣わなくていい
Because you and I are about to become rivals.
これからは 白鳥君と僕はライバルになるんだから
Why won't Shuujin come?
何で シュージンは来ないんだ
Does he want to work with Shiratori now?
もう白鳥君とやる気なのか
No, I have no time to worry about him.
いや シュージンの事を気にしている暇はない
I have to make the manga for the Love Fest!
僕は ラブフェスタの作品を作らないと
Otter No. 11 The End
You've worked hard on this over the years.
長い間 よく頑張った
I'm overwhelmed with emo—
僕も感無量だよ
Enough with that. Tell me what to do during my tea date with Aoki!
な事より 早く蒼樹さんとのお茶会のシナリオを
I'll help you out in exchange for a good storyboard for the one-shot.
それは面白い読切ネームと交換だ
Here.
ほらよ
Hiramaru Kazuya
"Never reaching you"
Storyboard
Hiramaru Kazuya
"Never reaching you"
Storyboard
Hiramaru Kazuya
"Never reaching you"
Storyboard
Hiramaru Kazuya
"Never reaching you"
Storyboard
Hiramaru Kazuya
"Never reaching you"
Storyboard
Hiramaru Kazuya
The protagonist is convinced he's so unpopular... This is great!
どこまでも自分は もてないと信じて疑わない主人公
I showed you!
面白い
It's the story of a boy who falls in love with an angel.
天使に恋する男の子のお話なんです
A love fantasy. That's just like you, Aoki.
蒼樹さんらしいラブファンタジーですね
You guys have any love experience?
お前ら 恋愛経験は
Nope!
ないっす
Only one-sided...
片思いなら
Useless.
使えねな
And you?
で 先生は
Idiots! I was the Romeo of Hiroshima!
バカヤロー
広島のロミオとは 俺の事だ
You're already done with the manuscript?
もう原稿UP
Can't stop the love!
愛は止まりません
What's with this character design?!
何ですか このキャラデザイン
The final climax isn't quite there.
ラストの盛り上がりがいまひとつだな
It just isn't expressed well.
何か うまく表現しきれていない
Okay. I still have time, right?
分かりました
まだ時間 ありますよね
Yeah. But everyone's already done except for you and Fukuda.
福田君以外は もうネーム 仕上がってるみたいだけどな
So this is the limit of what I can do alone...
やっぱり僕だけじゃ限界が
I have the image in my head, but I don't know how to express it through dialogue.
頭の中でイメージできても どうセリフにして 回していけばいいのか
Hattori, today is the serialization committee, right?
服部さん 連載会議 今日ですよね
Yeah, it just started.
さっき始まったところだ
If you're worried about Rabuta, I can call you with the results.
「恋太」の事が気になるんなら結果が出たら報告しようか
No, thats okay.
いえ
I'll redo my storyboard and send it to you again.
ネーム また直して送ります
They should have long since finished with the storyboard for the committee.
会議に出すネームはとっくに終わってるのに
So why aren't you here, Shuujin?
何で来ないんだ シュージン
"Go ahead and do Rabuta," I said.
「恋太」をやれって 俺の強がりだったんじゃないのか
Wasn't I just bluffing?
Huh? I turned in my manuscript yesterday.
あれ 原稿 昨日UPしたのに
Is that Kaya?
香耶ちゃん
Sorry, Saikou!
悪い サイコー
Shuujin!
シュージン
Today's the serialization committee, right?
今日は 連載会議だろ
Yeah.
Rabuta got in.
「恋太」は連載になった
Well, congrat—
とにかく おめで
Say that to Shiratori.
「おめでとう」は白鳥君に言ってくれ
It's all right now.
もう大丈夫だ
I helped out with chapters two and
three of the serialization storyboard,
連載ネームの23話は 手伝ったけど
but he did chapters four through seven himself.
そのあと7話までは完璧に1人で描かせた
He did? By  himself?
白鳥君1人で
Rabuta & Peace is a manga by Shiratori Shun, you know.
「恋太＆ピース」は 白鳥シュンの作品だからな
Shiratori had the talent to write the story all along.
もともと白鳥君には 話を作る才能もあったんだ
With a short training camp, he was able to do it.
短期間の合宿で 何とかものになってくれた
So you stayed over to Shiratori's place to make him independent?
じゃあ 白鳥君の所に行ったのは 1人立ちさせるために
Shiratori and Hattori both gave the
green light on going forward without me.
白鳥君も服部さんも この先は1人でやる事を 納得してくれた
You said you wanted me to do Rabuta, but I'm not that skilled.
サイコーは 「恋太」もやってほしいんだろうけど
俺には そんな器用なまねはできない
I'm fine with just Ashirogi Mutou's manga.
亜城木夢叶作品だけでいい
Now I can concentrate on PCP and the one-shot.
これで 「PCP」と読切作品だけに集中できる
Let's take the top spot in the Leader's Fest!
リーダーズラブフェスタで 1番 取ろうぜ
Shuujin! Hit me!
シュージン
俺を殴ってくれ
This is the end of Ashirogi Mutou!
もう亜城木夢叶も終わりだわ
It finally devolved into a fist fight!
ついに殴り合いのケンカまで
Stop it, both of you!
2人とも やめて
You were just "experiencing youth?" Don't make me laugh!
「青春してた」って ばっかじゃないの
You guys are too timid for that.
2人とも へっぴり腰だったし
We were both trying to cover for each other, but ended up wasting time and effort going in weird directions.
お互い かばい合ってるつもりが 空回りして変な方向いってたけど
Now we've cleared the air.
これでもう スッキリした
Let's go back to the studio and work on that storyboard for the Love Fest.
さっ 仕事場戻ってラブフェスタのネームやろうぜ
Yeah!
For starters, I think we should give the
protagonist a friend who makes wisecracks.
とりあえず 主人公には突っ込み役の親友つけた方がいい
I get it! Otherwise, the story between the protagonist and the heroine drags on and the setting stagnates...
そうか 主人公とヒロインだけで話が進むから 世界が狭くなってる
Yeah.
In the end, Aoki won it.
結局 蒼樹さんの一人勝ちだったな
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
We did better than Eiji and Iwase, though.
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
Love Story
One-shot Results
Within
1000 votes
1 What God gave me...
2 I Don't Understand
3 Boy E Girl B
4 A Small Time
5 LOVE power A to Z
6 Setsuna Yui
7 Fourberty
Aoki Kou
Hiramaru Kazuya
Arai Kisaku
Ashirogi Mutou
Niizuma Eiji
Fukuda Shinta
Akina Aiko
Hachihonki Hachirou
エイジや岩瀬には 勝ったけどな
But we did expand our horizons as Ashirogi Mutou.
でも これで亜城木夢叶の可能性幅は広がった
My drawing speed went up.
俺が絵を描くスピード 上がったしな
Yeah. Let's take our time, work on PCP,
焦らず 「PCP」を頑張って次の作品で アニメ化 狙おうぜ
and make our next manga into an anime.
Yeah!
Akito!
秋人さん
Mashiro!
真城
mogakinagara saikou no yume wo
The times when I fight and struggle and dream
katachi ni suru kono shunkan ga suki sa
of all the things I want in life is the best
tatakau you na te wo tsunagu you na
That's when I feel the bond between us and our strength to fight
kankaku ga shigekiteni da ne
Our view of the world overlaps and stimulates us
kousa shite
dakara motto migakou jibun rashiku arou
Let us polish ourselves, be more like how we should be
tsuzuita michi ni aru hazu
The future can be found on the path we walk
mirai wa
shinzuru mono ga chigau nakamatachi
My comrades believe in different things than me
Rival...and Friend!
butsukariau Pride
Our pride clashes
yuzurenai kore kara mo kokoro no mama susumou yo
I can't give up on it, I have to do what my heart commands me to do
junbi wa dekita
I'm ready
ikki ni kakeagaru tame no
I've got the unbending pride
akiramenai Pride
to run to the top now
hisshi nanda yo suki dakara suki wo mune ni susumu n da
This is my only choice, this is what I love and this is what I'll do
donna ashita ga matteru ka shiranai
I don't know what tomorrow will be like
asu mo
But I know that tomorrow, again,
bokura wa
girigiri
ganbatteru darou
we will do our best to get by
Next Time
Preview
Come on, Hiramaru.
さあ 平丸君 早く新連載をスタートさせよう
Let's hurry up and start your new serialization.
I want happiness more than a new series!
僕は次の連載より幸せがほしいです
I know. I'll do something about it.
わかった 俺がなんとかしてやる
Next time: Commemorative Photo Shoot and Classroom.
Commemorative Photo Shoot and
Classroom
My dream is to be joined with Aoki!
夢は 蒼樹さんと結ばれること です